Good evening traders, the
ICC Lombard stock today
showed the results of the previous day's 14.
So basically,
here
we heard some things about the company's expenditure levels and
here the ICC Bank stock has been
increased, so definitely there have been
some changes in the stock and here we
see some bullishness today. If
we
look at the quarters of ICC Lombard,
if we look at it, there is
some positive in the company, so the
market has broken the continuous 2 range today and this gap has
broken in you. At
this point, some
pending market activity, which means those who already knew something,
order five market days,
so here I would like to make stock judgment from the
trading perspective.
If I look at the market at the range of 114, if
I look at the market point, that is, the
point is particular from
this zone till
here, the
company stock is doing right now, then
find this one
which is the overall structure of the market.
If we look at the market structure,
then if there is no gap in this stock,
now look at this carefully, the stock does not have any gap
of single gap. Today
first a gap has been created here, so
we will try to see whether the gap is filled,
if the gap gets filled, here the
gap gets filled in the range of 1138 and second
think the range from 1138 to
1104.9 gets filled, then if
we get a downtrend
or inside out on this range or if
we get a bullish close after the graph gets filled, then if you want to sell the
stock from this perspective, then this can
become a perspective parameter,
so this is what I always say